<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2022-02-19T22:31:52.820+05:30"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        cq:template="/conf/aem-learn-components/settings/wcm/templates/page-content"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Cookie"
        sling:resourceType="aem-learn-components/components/page">
        <root
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="aem-learn-components/components/container"
            layout="responsiveGrid">
            <container
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="aem-learn-components/components/container"
                layout="responsiveGrid">
                <title
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="aem-learn-components/components/title"/>
                <container
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="aem-learn-components/components/container"
                    layout="responsiveGrid">
                    <text
                        jcr:created="{Date}2022-02-19T22:31:09.626+05:30"
                        jcr:createdBy="admin"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-02-19T22:31:52.817+05:30"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="aem-learn-components/components/text"
                        text="&lt;h3>General information&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>You are in control of your data.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>What are cookies and why does Adobe use them?&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>How do I make choices?&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;h3>If enabled:&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>We can improve your experience by tailoring the site and the content to things we think might be of interest&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>We can better keep track of your preferences — like what language you prefer to use&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>We will better understand your likely interests so we can provide you more relevant Adobe ads and content on non-Adobe websites and in non-Adobe apps&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>It will help us improve the performance of our website and those of our partners who use the Adobe Experience Cloud&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;h3>If disabled:&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>We won’t be able to remember you from session to session so the experience may not be tailored to your interests&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>You’ll still have access to the content of the site but certain features that depend on cookies may not function&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>You’ll still see ads, they just may not be as relevant to you&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;h4>Operate the site and core services&lt;/h4>&#xa;&lt;p>Always active&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>These cookies are required, and they are used to enable the site and related services core functionality. Without them the site could not operate, so they cannot be disabled.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h4>Measure performance&lt;/h4>&#xa;&lt;p>These cookies are used to analyze site usage to measure and improve performance. Without them Adobe cannot know what content is most valued and how often unique visitors return to the site, making it hard to improve information we offer to you.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h4>Extend functionality&lt;/h4>&#xa;&lt;p>These cookies are used to enhance the functionality of Adobe sites such as remembering your settings and preferences to deliver a personalized experience; for example, your username, your repeated visits, preferred language, your country, or any other saved preference.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h4>Personalize advertising&lt;/h4>&#xa;&lt;p>These cookies are used to enable Adobe and our partners to serve ads more relevant to your interests. Without them you will still see ads, but they might not be as relevant to you.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </container>
            </container>
        </root>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
